greetabl.com 2019-01-16

# Privacy Policy - Greetabl

**_Greetabl Privacy Policy_**   
Effective Date: 8/31/2018 

This Privacy Policy describes the practices that GREETINGQUBE, LLC d/b/a Greetabl (referred to as “Greetabl” or “we”) follows with respect to the collection, use, maintenance and disclosure of information collected through the website located at greetabl.com (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect from this Site, and does not apply to any other website or business activity of greetabl. By using our Site, you consent to the collection, use, maintenance and disclosure of this information by us. 

If you want to know what information we collect, why we collect it, and how it impacts you, then please take some time to read through our privacy policy: 

**_What Information Do We Collect?_**

a. **Personal Information** – Personal information is any information that is considered personally identifiable, like your name, email address, phone number, mailing address or payment information, that allows us to identify or contact you. When you create an account with us, edit or update your account information, upload images or other content to our Site, or order or use any of our products or services, we may collect personal information. 

We collect additional personal information when volunteered by you, such as information provided in surveys, blog comments, and emails. 

You can choose not to provide personal information to us. However, if you do not provide such information, you may not be able to make a purchase or create an account, so your ability to use the Site will be limited. 

b. **Uploaded Images & Content** – **** We may collect additional information that you submit to the Site when designing a mailer or other packaging, including text, photographs and other images. We may collect technical information about those photographs and images (such as the file size and aspect ratio). ****

c. **Usage Information & Cookies **– We may also collect “usage information”. It is information automatically collected by our web server (which may be hosted by a third-party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit or use our Site. For example, we may collect your IP address, browser type, operating system version, and information regarding your browsing activities (e.g., information about the websites that you visit before or after visiting the Site) and geographic location. ****

We may also use cookies to collect information. Cookies are tiny text files that are stored on your computer or mobile device. Cookies help us to facilitate your shopping process, including making it possible for us to store information regarding your design, image, text and other selections for a mailer or packaging that you are designing, and the contents of your shopping cart. By doing this, we can personalize your experience and save you time during checkout. 

It is possible to prevent cookies from being used by your browser. If you refuse to accept cookies, however, some portions of the Site may not function as intended. 

d. **Information Collected by Authorized Third Parties -** We work with third parties to monitor our website for the purposes of obtaining information regarding website traffic and other statistics. Where authorized by us, these third parties may use cookies and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. For example, this may include information regarding a visitor’s browsing activities, the pages and content viewed, the user’s geographic location, and the time and duration of visits **.** ****

**_California Do Not Track Disclosures_** **__** **__**

Greetabl does not respond to “do not track” signals. 

**_Use & Disclosure of Information_**

a. **General Use of Personal Information** – **** We use your personal information for the purpose that it was collected and for other purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use personal information to fulfill your requests for products and services, to process payments, to improve our services, to customize the content you see, to contact you, and for business/administrative and marketing/promotional purposes. 

b. **Uploaded Images & Content** – We may store photographs, images and other content uploaded or submitted to the Site - and information about any such photographs and images - in order to provide products and services, improve our products and services, garner insights and information about our users, and to fulfill orders. Our printing and assembly process requires human involvement, so greetabl employees and vendors will see your photographs, images and other content that you submit to the Site. We do not otherwise use the photographs, images or content in a manner that would identify you personally. 

c. **Usage Information** – We may use usage information in order to analyze trends, generally learn about usage of the Site, help us run and maintain our Site, and provide a better, more customized experience. 

d. **Referrals** – If you use our referral program to refer your friends to our Site, we will use the information you provide about your friends to contact them regarding your referral. We will retain such information in our systems and may use such information to verify whether such person ordered a product or visited the Site or to contact such persons to follow up on your referral. 

e. **Promotions & Surveys** – Every now and then, greetabl may invite customers to take part in surveys, promotions, contests and sweepstakes. The information we collect from these surveys, promotions, contests, and sweepstakes may be matched with individual customer accounts and used by Greetabl to contact you regarding our surveys, promotions, contests and sweepstakes and to improve your overall customer experience, and may be shared with third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf. 

f. **General Disclosure of Information** \- We may provide your personally identifiable information and usage information to third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf (e.g., those who help us fulfill or deliver your order, process payments, etc.). We may also disclose usage information to our affiliates and third parties, including, but not limited to, our advertisers. We may disclose your first name, last name and company name to recipients who have received a Greetabl that was sent by you. 

g. **Business Transfers** – We might sell or buy subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, personal information and usage information are generally some of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that our assets are sold, personal information and usage information may be one of the transferred assets. We may disclose personal information and usage information to affiliated companies, our parent company and sister companies. 

h. **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement** – We may use and disclose your personal information and usage information when we have reason to believe that using and/or disclosing this information is necessary to investigate, identify, contact, or take action against someone who may have engaged in illegal or unethical activities or breached our Terms of Use or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personal information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it. 

**_Storage of Information_**

a. **Location of Storage** – Any information, photographs, images or other content we collect may be transferred to and stored in our servers or those of third parties that act on our behalf (such as hosting providers) in the USA or elsewhere. By using our services you agree to such collection, transfer and storage. 

b. **Duration of Storage** – We may store any of your information, photographs, images and content for whatever duration we deem necessary to ensure that our records are accurate and complete. Such information, photographs, images and content may persist even after you delete your account. However, Greetabl does not operate as storage repository for your images or other content. If desired, you should make your own back-up and archival copies of any content, including images, that you upload or otherwise submit to the Site. We will not be liable to you for any loss of images or content. 

**_Access to Account Information and Preferences_**

a. **Changing Your Account Preferences** – You can opt in or out of our marketing communications and newsletter through your account preferences, or you can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages you receive. We do reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the goods and services greetabl provides, such as updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy, service/product announcements, administrative messages, or messages regarding any order you placed, which are considered part of your account membership. We do not offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving certain messages, including order confirmations and shipping notifications. 

b. **Modifying/Deleting Your Account** – If you have created an account, you may review, update, or correct personal information submitted in connection with that account by logging into your greetabl account and visiting the account preferences page. If you request that greetabl delete your account, we will use reasonable efforts to deactivate your account and delete your personal information in a timely manner, unless we are required to retain such information by law, or we reasonably believe we need to retain such information for business purposes. 

**_Privacy of Children_**

The Site is a general audience website. We do not intentionally collect personal information from users of this Site who are under the age of thirteen. ****

If we become aware that a user of our Site is under the age of 13 and has placed an order using our Site, we will remove that child’s personal information from our files. ****

**_Security_** ****

Information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet is not 100% secure. As a result, we do not ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such information. We will not be responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties. 

You help to maintain the security of your personal information stored in our systems by keeping your username and password confidential and protecting against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

**_Third Party Sites_**

Our Site may contain links to other websites for news and other information. Our Privacy Policy only applies to our Site, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites which are linked to or integrated with our Site. You should check the privacy policies of those sites before providing your personal information to them. 

**_Changes/Updates to the Privacy Policy_**

We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time. When we do, we will give you notice of the revised Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and by revising the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the current privacy policy. 

**_Questions and Suggestions_**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you can contact us at [hello@greetabl.com](mailto:hello@greetabl.com) with “Privacy Policy” in the subject line. ** __**

**greetabl** is a registered trademark of GREETINGQUBE, LLC, a corporation registered under the laws of the state of Missouri in the United States with our principal place of business at 1006 Olive St, Suite 2E, St. Louis, MO 63101.
